(朝鲜  非军事区)
大家动作快点  赶紧找到那个叛逃者
Hustle up, guys. You've got to get that defector
然后带离这里  不要耽搁
and get the hell out of there. No delays.
老鼠  准备好实现那个18岁目标了吗
Hey, Mouse, are you ready with that 18-year-old aim?
准备好了  长官
I'm on it, sir.
- 快  - 我们走
- Move. - Let's go.
快啊  这家伙到底在哪
All right, come on. Where is this guy at?
快啊  快啊  快啊
Come on, come on, come on. Come on, come on, come on.
老鼠  帮忙分散他们的注意力
All right, Mouse. Give us that diversion.
快走
Let's move.
火石  原地待命
Flint, stay put.
没人告诉你你打架超难看吗
Anyone ever tell you you fight ugly?
被我撂倒的人不会说话
Not from their backs, they don't.
只是...
It's just...
火石  走吧  火石
Flint, let's go. Flint?
你在搞什么鬼
What the hell are you doing?
标记一下我们的地盘  长官
Just marking our territory, sir.
大兵盖恩斯  看到火石的话  毙了他
Private Gaines, if you see Flint, shoot him.
乐意至极
With pleasure.
找到叛逃者了  返回撤离点  跟我走
Defector in hand. En route to pickup. Come on.
我没看到他  你呢
I don't see him, do you?
火石  快点滚回来
Flint, get your ass back to the team.
我们要撤退了
We are on the move.
你不会相信的  拦路虎
You ain't gonna believe this, Roadblock.
我日
Mother...
赢了
Yeah!
什么
What?
不不不  这不公平
No, no, no, no. No, no, no. Unfair advantage.
我更厉害点
I'm better.
他脸蛋很光滑  连胡须都没
He's got smooth cheeks. He's got no facial hair.
- 我要拉引信了  - 在水里摩擦力更小
- I'm gonna pull the pin. - There's less friction underwater.
那样算犯规  犯规
That's a foul. That's a foul.
这才是特种兵
A Joe flag.
这才是特种部队的队员
A G.I. Joe flag.
这招不错吧
That was a nice touch, right?
算是吧
Yeah. You can call it that.
那你觉得呢
And what would you call it?
- 很不光彩  - 也算是吧
- Undignified. - Yeah, that, too.
赢了就该绅士点
You know in victory, we should be gentlemen.
- 杰伊  - 在
-Hey, Jaye! - Yo!
普通人能屏住呼吸多久
How long can the average man hold his breath?
90秒
Ninety seconds.
- 给我来一瓶  - 没问题  老板
- Free hand. - You got it, boss.
好的  放轻松  小样
All right. Easy, Flipper.
拿着  妈的  这就不行了
Back. Damn, that's good.
胜利了庆祝一下很正常  这样才好玩
There's nothing wrong with taking a victory lap. It's fun.
事实就是这样  特种部队就像一个拳头
This is how it works. G.I. Joe's a fist.
我们就是指关节
Us, we're the knuckles.
我们要如何攻击
How do we strike?
团结在一起才行
Together.
若有一个手指没握紧
A finger strays...
- 就会被拗断  - 就会被拗断
- It gets broken. - It gets broken.
又来指关节了  你不是吧
Knuckles, again? Really?
友情提醒  下次换个新的故事
As a friend, you've got to get a new speech.
还有  下次你要淹某人
And the next time you want to drown somebody,
记得叫上我
just invite me.
《特种部队2：全面反击》
纳米虫战争结束后
Since the end of the Nanomite wars,
上尉公爵·豪泽尔指挥着特种部队的战术行动
Captain Duke Hauser now leads Joe Tactical Operations.
麾下成员有拦路虎
Under Duke's command are Roadblock,
杰伊女郎
Lady Jaye,
火石
Flint,
还有蛇眼
and Snake Eyes.
而残暴的恐怖分子眼鏡蛇指挥官
The ruthless terrorist known as Cobra Commander,
和迪斯特罗
and Destro
已经被特种部队抓获
have been captured by the G.I. Joes
并被关押在守备最森严的监狱里
and placed in a maximum security prison.
但是眼镜蛇特工  白幽灵
But the Cobra operatives, Storm Shadow
和扎坦  仍然逍遥法外
and Zartan, remain at large.
特种部队和整个世界
The unit and the world
都在高度警戒眼鏡蛇指挥官最后的誓言
remain on high alert following Cobra Commander's final vow.
全面反击
Retaliation.
(日本  东京)
听风辨影
The ear that sees.
岚影一族传承已久的测试
An ancient Arashikage test.
金克斯  白幽灵的表妹
Jinx, cousin to Storm Shadow,
是时候证明你有能力加入特种部队了
it's time to prove that you are ready to join the G.I. Joes.
保护好你自己
Defend yourself.
准备好了  盲大师
I'm ready, Blind Master.
耳听八方
Ears, open.
蛇眼  你来测试她
Snake Eyes, your task.
测试她的能力
Test her abilities.
拔下金克斯的一根头发
Pluck a single hair from Jinx's head.
开始
Hajimate!
不错不错
Ah, good.
要像猫一样敏捷
One should be as nimble as a cat,
还要像老虎一样凶猛
yet fierce as a tiger.
蛇眼获胜
Snake Eyes wins.
金克斯  为了在战场获胜
Jinx, in order to excel in war,
你首先就要学会沉着冷静
you must first find peace.
蛇眼
Snake Eyes,
你赢得了正义之刃
you have earned the Blade of Justice.
此刀由黑色碳纤维打造
Made of black carbon fibre.
凶残无比且坚不可摧
Cruel. Indestructible.
传言我们的敌人即将卷土重来
There are rumours of a new attack by our enemies.
你要离开道场  找出并阻止他们的计划
You must leave the dojo to uncover these plans and stop them.
迅速行动  你可能已经晚了
But move swiftly. You may already be too late.
正面遇敌  正面遇敌
Contact front! Contact front!
敌人火力很强
Heavy enemy fire!
守住防线  守住防线
I need you to bring them up the line. Bring them up the line.
收到  虎爷  但我赶不过去
Check that, Block, but I can't, man.
我被攻击了
I'm taking rounds back here.
我需要你的支援  现在就需要你的支援
I need you! I need you now!
发动空袭  快发动空袭
Air strike! Call in an air strike!
等等  怎样才能发动空袭来着
Wait. How do you call in an air strike?
- 老天  - 我能不能
- Jesus! - Can I bring...
能不能用个急救包之类的
What about one of those, like, care package thingies?
我都快死了  就等着你冲过来
I'm bleeding out and I need you to sprint.
能不能用急救包  我可以给你
Can you use a care package thingy? I can bring you one.
急救包
A care package thingy?
谁在朝我开枪  搞什么
Who is shooting me? What is...
我都快死了  你却在...
I'm bleeding out right there and you're...
你是在原地打转吗
Are you spinning?
我得全方位掩护你
You got to cover 360.
你在原地打转
You're spinning.
你实战打得那么好  玩这个烂死了
How could you be so good at combat? You stink at this.
别激动  我记得我的军衔
I think you need to relax. I believe I outrank you,
- 比你高  - 别在我的地盘摆架子
- last time I checked. - Not in my house, you don't.
好吧  敌军来袭
All right. Taking fire!
受到敌人攻击  暂停  受到敌人攻击
Enemy fire! Time out! Enemy fire!
遇敌
Enemy contact!
公爵叔叔  你耳朵好大
Uncle Duke, you have big ears.
你头好大  过来
You got a big head. Come here!
回击敌人  现在怎么样
Returning fire! What's up, now?
回击敌人
Returning fire!
尖叫也没用的
You can't scream your way out of this one!
请求支援  虎爷
Yeah, requesting assistance, brother Block!
无法动弹  公爵  无法动弹
Pinned down, brother Duke. Pinned down.
没关系  我还有我的伙伴  地狱犬
That's all right. I got my boy here. Demon dog!
奶奶  帮帮我们  我们需要后援
Grandma, help us! We need backup!
这可不是你第一次
Not the first time you sent a girl
让女孩子尖叫着逃跑了
running out of the room screaming.
也不是第一次让两个女孩子尖叫着逃跑
Not the first time I sent two girls screaming from a room.
兄弟  这玩笑开得太不合适了
Dude, completely inappropriate.
- 说说而已  - 太不合适了
- I'm just saying. - Completely.
总统被暗杀之后
Violence continues across Pakistan
巴基斯坦首都伊斯兰堡
in the capital of Islamabad
持续发生暴力袭击事件
following the assassination of President...
因为暗杀所造成的权力真空
The future of the country and control of its nuclear arsenal
这个国家的未来
appear to be up in the air.
以及对其核武器的控制都成了未知数
as the vacuum created by the killing remains.
(华盛顿哥伦比亚特区)
就算巴基斯坦的总统死了
The Pakistani President may in fact be dead,
巴基斯坦仍然是我们的盟国
but Pakistan remains an ally.
并且是个主权国家
And a sovereign nation.
曾经是
Was.
现在  那里不过是一个发生暴乱的地区
Right now, they're a riot with a zip code.
长官  我们在这里争论的时候
Sir, every minute we spend debating this,
骚乱地区正潜伏着已激活的核弹头
there are live nuclear warheads that sit amidst the chaos.
我们不能让敌人抢先拿到这些弹头
We can't let our enemies get those warheads first.
都有什么建议
Recommendations?
潜入
Go in.
立刻潜入
Now.
静观其变
Wait and see.
狭路相逢勇者胜
History rewards the bold.
我不会当那个坐视不理的人
I'm not going to be the man who waited and saw.
帮我把特种部队找来
Get me the G.I. Joes.
星际一号指挥官准备行动
Star One Flight commander separating for drop.
都给我听好了
All right, listen up!
核弹头应该就在附近  一抢到手
That nuke cannot have gone far. Once we have it,
返回着陆点的途中就立即解除激活
we will disarm it en route to the L.Z.!
弹头的位置
We have its location narrowed down
在这个导弹装配工厂内某处
to somewhere in this missile assembly building.
我们从楼顶进入  之后分开行动
We'll go in on the roof, and fan out from there.
火石  杰伊  如果别人需要支援
Flint, Jaye, if any support is needed,
你们当援兵  拦路虎带领地面部队
you'll reinforce as Roadblock leads the ground team.
遵命
Hell, yeah.
老鼠
Hey, Mouse.
我第一次跳伞的时候放了颗子弹在嘴里
On my first drop I popped a live round into my mouth.
这样牙齿就不会打颤了  试试看
Keeps your teeth from chattering. Give it a shot.
- 真好吃  - 好小子
- Delicious. - Attaboy.
杰伊  敌人装备如何
Jaye, what are we up against?
叛军用的都是卡拉什尼科夫冲锋枪
Insurgents are armed with Kalashnikovs,
SVD狙击步枪还有50式冲锋枪
SVD Dragunovs and Type 50s.
都是冷战时期的古董了
Cold War stuff.
别掉以轻心  还是能把你们打个稀巴烂
But don't relax, boys, still put holes in you.
你拿的是什么
Whoa! What have you got there?
P381黑风暴  全新的
P-dub 381 Black Tempest, just out of the box.
可绕行  0.25倍速  远程遥控
Rounds. Quarter speed, remote controlled.
我们什么时候才能有
When did we get these?
你们没门  只有我们两个有
We didn't. We did.
一流枪手专用
Distinguished Marksmen.
- 让我看看  - 手别碰
- Let me see. - Don't touch.
玩枪的女孩惹不起
Girls with guns.
接近目标位置  注意  做好准备
Approaching target. Ten-hut! Make ready!
出发  出发  出发
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
有谁想蛇眼了吗
Anyone else missing Snake Eyes?
我跟蛇眼在一起训练了六年
I trained with Snake for six years.
他不在这儿一定有自己的原因
If he ain't here, he's got good reason.
大天使号  准备就位
Arch-Angel, go for drop.
虎爷  老规矩
Brother Block, as always,
给我们讲几句吧  好吗
would you mind leading us in a few words, please, sir?
引用一下Jay-Z(美国HipHop歌手)的名言
In the immortal words of Jay-Z,
无论是何方神圣在指引我
"Whatever deity may guide my life,
亲爱的主  别让我在今夜死去
"Dear Lord, don't let me die tonight.
若只能止步于此  在我苏醒之前
"But if I shall, before I wake,
我愿接受我的命运
"I accept my fate."
大胆上吧
Hell, yeah?
Hell, yeah!
大胆上吧
Hell, yeah.
武器检查
Equipment check!
- 完毕  - 完毕
- Check! - Check!
- 完毕  - 就当你的枪是偷来的
- Check! - Drive it like you stole it!
友情提醒  你需要一句新口头禅
As your good friend, you need a new catchphrase.
A队  B队  通讯检查
Alpha, Bravo, radio check.
收到
Copy.
未被发现前不要暴露
Go in ghost till first contact.
- 三队和六队到达一楼  - 收到
- Three and six on the floor. -Copy that.
二队  大量敌人来袭  开火
Team two, expect heavy contact. Bring the rain!
行动
Move out!
三队  往楼上移动
Team three headed upstairs.
东侧走廊已安全
East hallway, clear.
二层清理完毕  正在往三层移动
Level 2 secure. Moving to level 3.
- 欠你一个人情  老鼠  - 安全
- I owe you one, Mouse. - Clear!
我看到核弹头了
All right! I got eyes on the nuke!
重复一遍  我看到核弹头了
Say again, I got eyes on the nuke!
但我正受到攻击
But I'm taking heavy fire!
在那别动  我马上绕道过去
Sit tight! I'm taking a detour!
不行  火石  照计划行事
Negative, Flint! Stick with the plan!
敌人已消灭
Tangos down!
快  快  快
Go, go, go!
火石  报告情况
Flint, status!
开火
Fire it out!
核武器已到手
Weapons secured!
- 弹头运输装置在四楼  - 好了
- Equipment pack-up on level 4! -Set!
克拉奇  到运输车的位置去  快点
Clutch, station the transport vehicle! Move!
所有小队  准备撤退  抓紧时间
All teams, rally to transpo, immediately.
叛军正在逼近  长官
Insurgents closing in, sir!
二队安全  无人员损失
Team two secure. No losses.
- 联系司令部  - 这就去
- Contact headquarters. -I'm on that.
快上车  我们撤退
Mount up! Let's exfil.
- 路线确认安全  - 快上车
- Run way secure. - Let's mount up!
核武器已解除激活状态
Nuke's disabled.
准备进行远距离运输  大概19点到达
Long-range transportation and wheels down at 1900 hours.
还能赶回家看《顶级厨师》
Home in time for Top Chef.
干得漂亮  小蒂姆
Good job, Tiny Tim.
任天堂的射击游戏玩多了也有好处啊
All that Wii Combat Shooter finally paying off, sir.
- 你好  长官  - 好
- How you doing, sir? - Good.
所有特种兵都已安全归队
All Joes present and accounted for.
报告下情况
Sit rep?
已经确认安全并且准备好运输了  长官
Rendered safe and ready for transport, sir.
搞定后去喝一杯吧
Square this one away and go get a beer.
那真不错
Sounds good.
(弗吉尼亚州  蒙特克莱尔  总统行宫)
长官  核武器已找回并解除激活状态
Sir, the nukes have been recovered and disabled.
特种部队任务圆满完成
All Joe missions successful.
只有一些人员轻微受伤  长官
Only minor injuries to report, sir.
运输队正在着陆点准备  凌晨两点撤离
Transport crews are prepping the L.Z. for evac at 0200 hours.
干得漂亮  上尉
Great job, Captain.
我们正在修改你们的撤离计划
We're modifying your extraction plan back here.
原地待命
Sit tight.
走吧  里韦拉  走吧
Let's go, Rivera, let's go.
我直说了吧
Let me get this straight.
整个周末
One whole weekend,
你照顾我的女儿
you looking after my little girls.
行  只要我能带着这把枪去
Yep, as long as I can bring this.
我真的很喜欢你的女儿
Look, I love your kids. I do.
但她们太会折磨我了  你教女有方
But they live to terrorise me. You trained them well.
那如果你赢了呢
And if you win?
你必须接受下一次升职
You have to take your next promotion.
你扣一下扳机  我扣一下扳机
You pull a trigger, I pull a trigger.
我很怀疑你到底有多大能耐
I don't know if I'm gonna trust a pastry from a gumbo chef.
风也是影响因素
Think about the wind.
7.5公里  从左到右
Four knots? Left to right.
我猜湿度是62%左右
Humidity, I say, is about 62%.
你还打算告诉我气压是吗
You gonna feed me the barometric pressure, too?
气压在升高  就像你勃起时的内裤一样
That's on the rise. Like your panties.
你爱死我的内裤了
You love my panties.
这笑话真是莫名其妙
That's an interesting choice of a joke.
你有这么多笑话可以说
Of all the things you could say...
什么叫"你爱死我的内裤了"
"You love my panties"?
你能闭嘴吗
Are you gonna shut up?
- 到底什么意思  - 你能闭嘴吗
- What does that mean? - You gonna shut up?
- 我在帮你  - 我这准备射击呢
- I'm looking out for you. - I'm trying to do something.
- 我只是  - 闭嘴  给我闭嘴
- I just don't... - Shut up, just shut up.
- 说说而已  - 给我  闭嘴
- I'm just saying. - Just shut up.
你的心跳多少
How's your heart rate?
这个不算
That is not gonna count.
你说话干扰我了  我要重来一次
I get to go again because you talked.
你已经扣了一次扳机  现在轮到我了
You pulled a trigger. Now I pull a trigger.
不行  不带这样的
No, we're not doing that.
这样做不算数
That is not gonna count.
你作弊
Cheater.
我给我女儿买了一台卡拉OK机
I bought my little girls a karaoke machine
而且她们特别喜欢通宵欢唱
and they love singing on it, all night long.
没有宵禁  所以她们会玩通宵
There's no bedtime curfew, so they're going to be up all night.
别忘了带耳塞
Make sure you bring your earplugs.
- 我们玩三局两胜吧  - 不要
- C'mon, best two out of three. - No.
三局两胜  刚刚那个不算
Best two out of three. That didn't count.
你没告诉我你买了卡拉OK机
You didn't tell me about the karaoke machine.
詹达
Zandar.
总统先生
Mr. President.
你不是该保护我爸爸不被坏人攻击吗
Aren't you supposed to stop people from shooting my dad?
死秃驴
Baldy.
白痴
Idiot.
够了  李·哈维(刺杀肯尼迪的凶手)
Enough out of you, Lee Harvey.
快给我去清理干净
Go clean up the chocolate stains
你留在你妈房间里的巧克力污迹
you left in your mother's bedroom.
小猫要抓人咯
Kitty likes to scratch.
有机会
Next time,
把这个胖墩干掉
take out his fat ass.
乐意至极  总统先生
It would be my pleasure, sir.
告诉你件事
I brought you some news.
特种部队马上就要消失了
The G.I. Joes are about to be out of the picture.
"马上要消失"的意思是
And by "Out of the picture," I mean
把他们打回原形
alive on earth.
他们太具威胁性了
Got a little too close to Mount Olympus.
必须把他们赶尽杀绝
Had to strike them down.
他们会找到你的  扎坦
They'll find you out, Zartan.
不  他们找不到的
No. No, I don't think so.
这就是纳米虫的厉害之处
That's the beauty of Nanomites.
来  让你见识一下
Here, take a look.
完美无瑕的微技术
Flawless microtechnology.
你个疯子
You're insane.
闲话少说  让他坐下
Recess over. Sit him down.
都说当总统是吃力不讨好的事
You know, they say this is a thankless job.
但是昨天我居然和博诺(爱尔兰摇滚乐队U2的主唱)出去玩了
But yesterday I hung out with Bono.
我的新特勤处
My new Secret Service,
想把美国宪法给烧了
they want to burn the Constitution.
真心想
Literally.
还有我那些实习生
And my interns...
是的  我把实习生都带回来了
Oh, yeah, I brought back the interns.
知道我最喜欢什么吗  可以随便炸东西
Do you know my favourite bit? I get to blow stuff up.
真是个讨人喜欢的做法
I bet that endears you to the people.
一点没错
Well, that's the thing.
你的支持率上升了9个百分点
Your approval ratings climbed nine points.
显然  美国民众想要一个面容如你
Apparently, America wants someone who looks like you,
但行动如我的总统
but acts like me.
我这张嘴很能说哦
I'm the quicker blower-upper, baby.
只有一个弊端
Only one drawback.
想你的小娇妻吗
The little wifey-pooh?
你若敢动我家人
If you touch my family...
我开玩笑的
I'm yanking your chain.
你当了两届总统
Two long terms of you,
我只当了几个月
just a few short months of me.
所以就别浪费我剩下的这点时间了
So let's not waste the time I got left.
关押眼镜蛇指挥官和迪斯特罗的监狱在哪
Where is the prison that holds Cobra Commander, and Destro?
我应该问你  你葫芦里卖的是什么药
Is this where I ask you, what do you have planned?
知道为什么大家都想做总统吗
Why does anyone want to be President?
因为人人都想统治世界
Everybody wants to rule the world.
各小队  带好行装  离开着陆点
All squads, gear up and clear the L.Z.
准备撤离
Prepare for extraction.
什么叫拔出  我们是牙齿吗
Extraction? What are we, teeth?
- 联系上总部了吗  - 还没有
- Reach H.Q.? - No, I got nothing.
- 到高处试试  - 明白  长官
- Go up high. - Roger, Sarge.
虎爷
Block.
所有人都归队了  一滴血都没流
All our men accounted for. Not a single drop of blood.
- 完胜  - 没错
- Boots to asses. - Yes, sir.
除了  你擦伤了手肘吗
Except for that... Did you scrape your elbow?
- 没  红汗症而已  - 好吧
- No, it's red sweat. - Yup.
最好是你打人后留下的血
That better have been on somebody's face.
公爵
Hey, Duke.
你看
You see that?
保安部队来早了
Security's early.
- 趴下  - 找掩护
- Get down! - Take cover!
找掩护
Take cover!
拿起武器  走
To your weapons! Let's go!
卧倒  卧倒
On the ground! On the ground!
老鼠
Mouse!
把他们赶出着陆点
Get 'em out of the L.Z.!
需要医护
Medic!
快走
Go!
火石被击中了  火石被击中了
Flint's down! Flint's down!
- 我去救他  - 快去
- I'm going for him! - Go!
注意10点钟方向
Ten o'clock!
趴下
Get down!
部队遇袭  请求紧急空中支援
Troops in contact! Request immediate air support!
重复一遍  请求紧急空中支援
I repeat, immediate air support!
没事吧  快  我们得离开这里  走
You all right? Come on, we got to move! Go, go, go!
你没事吧  受伤了吗
You good? You hit?
虎爷  火石安全了  我们需要掩护
Block, I got Flint. We got to get to cover!
起来
Come on.
敌机来袭  快跑  快跑
Incoming! Incoming! Go, go, go, go, go!
公爵  回话
Duke, come in.
公爵
Duke!
快找掩护
Get to cover, now!
- 撤退  回集结点  - 快走
- Go! Pull back! Rally point! - Let's go!
跳进井里去  快
Get to the well! Go!
快离开
Clear 'em out of there.
撤退
Fall back!
检查完毕
We're clear.
走吧
Let's go!
我们知道了敌人的身份
We have met the enemy.
(美国总统发表全国讲话)
敌人就是我们
And he is us.
今天  世界精英战斗队伍  特种部队
Today, the world's elite fighting force, the G.I. Joes,
摈弃了他们的职责
abandoned their duty
打破了他们与美国人民以及把人身安全
and broke the sacred bond that exists between the American people
托付给他们的人之间神圣的约定
and those entrusted with their security.
预备  走
Ready and step.
预备
Ready and
走
step!
巴基斯塔总统率先遇刺
The first domino fell with the murder of the Pakistani president.
刺客是
The assassin,
一名特种兵
a Joe,
代号
call sign
蛇眼
Snake Eyes.
但他并非单独作案
But he didn't act alone.
特种部队企图利用当前局势
The Joes intended to use this situation
夺取巴基斯坦的核武库
to seize Pakistan's nuclear arsenal.
这次事件
Now this incident
让我们清醒地认识到核武器带来的灾祸
serves as a sobering reminder of the scourge of nuclear weapons.
为此
And to that end,
我号召世界领袖们
I call upon my fellow world leaders
马上聚集起来讨论
to convene immediately to discuss
核裁军的问题
nuclear disarmament.
我数三下
On three.
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three!
特种部队的行为已明显越线
The G.I. Joes clearly went beyond the boundaries of their mission.
在我的指挥下
On my orders
一个代号为眼镜蛇的秘密特种部队
a covert Special Forces unit code named Cobra
消灭了特种部队
terminated with extreme prejudice Joe Command,
破坏其设备并歼灭全员
facilities, personnel.
特种部队已不复存在
The G.I. Joes are no more.
我们得离开
We should leave.
这里什么都没有了
There's nothing here.
什么都没有了?
There's nothing left here?
- 他不是那个意思  - 这里有我们兄弟
- That's not what he meant! - These are our brothers!
他不是那个意思
That's not what he meant!
袭击我们的人还会回来的
Whoever did this is going to come back.
我们得转移
We need to move.
你现在是我们的指挥官
You are our leader now.
我们向正东前进直到摆脱危险
We head due east until we're clear.
我们一定会找出是谁杀害了公爵
We're gonna find the man who did this to Duke
和兄弟们
and our brothers.
然后杀了他
And we're gonna kill him.
(艾恩萨根地下监狱)
蛇眼
Snake Eyes.
竟然能在这里见到你
Last place I thought I'd see you.
我是监狱长詹姆斯  很荣幸见到你
Warden James. It's a pleasure.
我可是你的大粉丝  我喜欢这身黑衣服
I'm a very big fan. I love the black.
很有约翰尼·卡什(美国乡村音乐歌手)的风格
It's very Johnny Cash.
来  欢迎你来到艾恩萨根
Come. Welcome to Einsargen.
我来给你介绍一下这个地方
Let me tell you a little bit about the place.
看看我  像个房地产经纪人一样
Listen to me. I sound like a real-estate agent.
我可不是来卖东西给你的
I'm not here to sell you anything.
也许只剩绝望可以给你了
Except maybe hopelessness.
旅途愉快吗
How was your trip?
开始觉得头晕目眩了吗
The sensation that you're feeling, your upside-down tummy?
因为我们正在下降到前东德的一个矿井里
It's due to our descent into a former East German mine shaft.
这是他们最深的一个矿井
It was the deepest they ever dug.
事实上  你刚刚已经离开德国
So deep in fact that you just crossed out of Germany
进入了国际领地
into international territory.
这也给了我
Which allows me
一定的权限自由
certain jurisdictional freedoms.
一句话
One word,
棒极了  这个房间简直棒极了
awesome. This room is awesome!
这里的温度原本超过摄氏100度
Temperatures here exceed 210 degrees
但人工降到了摄氏20度
when not artificially cooled to a crisp 68.
都差点要盖毛毯了
Almost calls for a Snuggie.
看完下一个再惊叹吧
Wait till you see this next one.
懂了吧  这里简直秒杀了我
See what I mean? This just slays me.
太有趣了  这里就要用到科学了
It's so interesting. This is where science has come.
你知不知道  在快速眼动睡眠阶段时
Did you know that during REM sleep
人类的身体
the human body
会制造出一种神经化学物质
produces a neural chemical
它能够麻痹除了心脏和眼睛以外的
which paralyses every muscle in the body
全身肌肉  从而阻止
but the heart and the eyes? This prevents us
我们梦游
from acting out our dreams.
这两人已被注入
We have injected both of these men
一种类似的合成物质
with a synthetic version.
他们完全醒着  有意识
They're perfectly awake. They're conscious,
能察觉到周围的一切事物
they're aware of everything that's going on around them.
他们只是被困在自己的身体里了
It's just that they're trapped inside themselves.
你应该认识你的新邻居吧  这是迪斯特罗
Well, I believe you know your new neighbours, Destro,
这是眼镜蛇指挥官
Cobra Commander.
你们三个就像是我的橄榄球梦之队
Oh, the three of you are like my fantasy football team.
带走
Gentlemen.
既然你东张西望
Now as your eyes and mind
心不在焉  那我就让你痛苦一下
travel to where you cannot, I want you to agonise.
让你吃点苦头
I want you to pine.
让你为即将逝去的自由而痛心
I want you to ache for what once was and will never be again.
我要让你觉得"逃走"这个词根本不存在
I want you to doubt that there was ever a word for escape.
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
你什么都不懂
You have no idea.
蛇眼说话了
Snake Eyes speaks.
虽然从没想过你的声音会是怎样
It never occurred to me what you might sound like, but...
但我却构想过你的模样
I've always thought about what you might look like.
脱下他的面具
We'll have that mask.
白幽灵
Storm Shadow.
是你把巴基斯坦总统干掉了
So you killed the Pakistani president.
你并不是我的首选
Well, you're not exactly my first-round draft pick,
不过我一直都很欣赏你
but I've always been a fan.
按规矩我们该发出求救呼叫  对吧
Protocol says we make a distress call, right?
不行  部队都没了  规矩也就没了
No. Protocol died with the unit.
什么
What?
别人怎么知道我们没死
How's anybody gonna know we're alive?
他们不用知道  因为我们已经死了
They're not, 'cause we're not.
对于我们的政府
To our government,
家人  特别是敌人来说
to our families, but especially to our enemy,
我们凌晨六点在印度河谷荒漠被杀
we were KIA at 0600 hours in the Indus Valley Desert.
但我们至少得试试  也许有人...
But we have to at least try. I mean, there might be someone...
不  我们现在做什么都要绝对保密
No. Anything we do now is a rumour of a rumour.
所有能证明我们活着的证据都没了
Any and all traces of our existence is terminated.
我所信任的也只有蛇眼一人
The only one I trust out there is Snake Eyes.
什么时候袭击我们
When we got hit,
怎样袭击我们
how we got hit,
从一开始这局就已设好
we were set up right from the start.
能下令发动这种袭击的人
How many stars would someone need on their shoulder
肩章上得有几颗星  四颗还是五颗
to call an attack like that? Four? Five?
不是肩章上有星的  是衣服上有扣子的
No, not stars. Buttons on his suit.
可能是国家安全顾问  或者国防部长
National Security Advisor. Secretary of Defence.
不  能发动这种袭击的只有一个人
No. There's only one man who could authorise a strike like that.
我还给他投过票
And I voted for him.
眼镜蛇指挥官生命体征稳定
All vitals on Cobra Commander are steady.
神经抑制剂已注入白幽灵体内
Storm Shadow nerve prohibitors injected.
摄氏17度  变化幅度4%
Sixty-two degrees on a change of 4%.
- 空袭  - 趴下
- Aerial threat! - Down!
我们回家
We're going home.
心脏停了
Full arrest!
快  这不是演习  把手铐拿来
Quickly! No drill! Bring the restraints!
打开容器盖子
Remove the containment lid!
血清在哪里  快点
Where's the serum? Quickly!
肾上腺素  快点  肾上腺素
Adrenaline now. Now! Adrenaline!
快点  快  快
Let's go! Quickly, quickly!
不要磨叽
Move! Move!
血清在哪里
Where's the serum?
快上
Let's go!
到后面去  快点
Peel back! Move!
什么叫他没有心跳了
What do you mean, his heart stopped beating?
除非我下令  这里不准有人死掉
No one here dies unless I say so!
我的天
Oh, my God.
开枪
Fire!
快开枪  开枪
Fire! Fire!
把他拿下
Take him down!
北边没有异常
Clear on the north!
安全
Clear!
欢迎来到地狱
Welcome to hell.
停住
Stop!
不许让人活着走出那扇门
You shoot anything that walks through that door!
都给我毙了
Anything!
白幽灵
Storm Shadow.
真靠得住
Never a doubt.
眼镜蛇指挥官
Cobra Commander.
迪斯特罗
Destro.
你出局了
You're out of the band.
出来啊
Come on.
快出来
看来你找了人来接应
I see you've arranged transportation.
我在早上9点前炸掉的东西
Making more things go boom by 9:00 a.m.
比其他人一天能炸掉的还多
than most people do all day.
萤火虫  很高兴见到你  老伙计
Firefly. Good to see you, old friend.
长官
Sir.
可就是有人不让我进来
Some people just didn't want to let me in.
我逃出过八座监狱
Now, I busted out of eight prisons.
闯监狱还是第一次
But I only broke into one.
所有通信已被切断
All communications have been cut off.
没有人会知道你不见了
No one will know you're even missing.
把他带去山里治疗
Take him to the mountains to heal.
在接下来要发动的战争里  还用得着他
I'll need him for the war I'm about to start.
我想帮你的忙
I want to help you.
白幽灵受伤了  我们清楚他要去哪
We've seen Storm's injuries. We know where he's headed.
你需要我
And you need me.
好
Good.
(宙斯工业综合体)
长官  发射操控中心就快建好了
Sir, launch controls are nearly up.
一直是主管在主持大局
The director was running behind.
这里再也不归他管了
Well, he ain't running behind no more.
其它地方也是
Or anywhere else, for that matter.
盔甲已按您的要求制作完成
Armour prototype is complete to your specs.
我今天把马力加到了60
I got it up to 60 on the dyno today.
它的名字您一定喜欢
You'll like this. Working title,
高速哨兵  HISS
High Speed Sentry. HISS.
欢迎您回来  长官
It's good to have you back, sir.
很美吧
Ain't she a beauty?
这个世界很快就会臣服于宙斯的脚下
Soon the world will cower in the face of Zeus.
现在只差我们的指挥官了
All we've been missing is our Commander.
面具不错
Cool mask.
有人迟到了
Someone took his time.
要从那个又大又白  有11间卧室
Not easy to sneak out of that big, white,
35个半浴室的房子里溜出来很不容易
11-bedroom, 35-and-a-half bath...
别忘了是谁帮你坐到现在的位置
Just don't forget who put you there.
也别忘了你的卑贱出身
Or the rock you crawled out from.
萤火虫  还好我们的疯狂不减当年
Firefly. It's good to know we're not running low on crazy.
十只手指还健全吧
Still all 10 fingers?
前任总统怎么样了
How is our former President?
他价值连城
He is worth his weight in platinum.
有人说当总统很无聊
You know, they call it a waterboard,
但我一点都不觉得
but I never get bored.
48小时后  宙斯就能发射
In 48 hours, Zeus will launch.
有个小问题
Just one wrinkle.
有三个特种兵在这次围剿中逃生了
Three Joes somehow survived our little house cleaning.
无人机在印度河谷捕捉到了他们的声音
A drone picked up voiceprints in the Indus Valley.
我还能指望你办成什么事情
Can I trust you with nothing?
他们会露出马脚的
They'll slip up.
一旦露出马脚
And when they do,
我就去解决他们
I'll hunt them to ground.
没事  你们看着
No, no, it's cool.
我来就好
I got it.
迷路了吗  小朋友
You lost, little man?
不  我没迷路
No, I ain't lost.
你走错路了
I think you got the wrong street.
你还是带着麦莉·赛勒斯(美国女演员)
So why don't you take Miley Cyrus
和瑞安·西克雷斯特(美国电视节目主持)
and Ryan Seacrest
往回走吧
and head back that way?
我走这边
I'm going that way.
是吗
Oh. Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
那好吧  马文
Go ahead, Marvin.
拜托  别这样叫我
Man, don't call me that name.
你还好吧  小马文
What's up? Little Marvin!
- 马文?  - 现在是大马文了
- Marvin? - Big Marvin now.
你吓到了嘛  兄弟
Had you worried for a minute, man.
当心你的包  被抢走就不好了
Watch your handbag there, boy. You don't want them to get you.
你看看你  块头这么大了
Look at you. You got grown.
你爸妈怎么让你长那么壮的啊
How your parents make a kid this big, man?
- 他父母都只有1米57  - 真的吗
- His parents are like 5'2" apiece. - Really?
你按《90天魔鬼训练法》训练了吧
You're taking that P90X serious, huh?
一周练两次呢
Twice a week.
瞧你脖子那么粗就知道了
I see. Look at the size of your neck.
我来介绍一下  这是火石
Let me introduce you. This is Flint.
你好
What up?
杰伊女郎
Lady Jaye.
杰伊女郎  你好
Lady Jaye. Hey.
- 欢迎回来  - 谢谢
- Welcome back. - Thank you.
遇到困难时就会回家
It's what happens when you're in trouble, you come home.
家就是避风港
Home is where the help is.
阿门
Amen.
我们会帮你们的
Well, we got you.
你们去娱乐中心住
Set up at the rec centre.
避避风头  没人会来打扰你
Lay low over there. Nobody gonna bother you.
要用车的话
As far as wheels go,
就用我的卡车吧
I'm gonna let you roll my truck.
谢谢
Thank you.
以前我就是开这车去收保护费的  兄弟
I got payments on that truck, man.
钱不像以前那样好赚了
I don't get it like I used to. All right?
谢谢了  斯多普
Thank you, Stoop.
我欠你一个人情  兄弟
I owe you one, brother.
事实上  你欠了两个
Actually, you owe me two.
那次不算
That other one don't count.
欢迎回家  马文
Welcome home, Marvin.
注意脚下
Watch your step.
这里很多年没人来了
No one's been here for years.
这暂时就是我们的窝了
This is gonna have to be our pit for now.
这还真乱得跟狗窝一样
Wow. It's an actual pit.
我以前经常来这里
It's my old stomping ground.
我们真的可以信任这个斯多普吗
Are you sure we can trust this Stoop guy?
斯多普不是天使
Stoop's no angel.
但他是家人  可以信任
But he is family and we can trust him.
我们会不会被追踪
Can we be traced?
我们可以将IP地址隐藏起来
We can mask our IP addresses.
我会每六小时发送一次加密信号
I'll cyber-blast an encoded beacon every six hours.
如果有特种兵幸存下来了
If any Joes did survive,
我们得让他知道我们在哪
we need to let them know where we're at.
好吧  开始吧
All right. Well, let's get to work.
火石  列出我们所剩的武器
Flint, inventory every piece of equipment we got left.
杰伊  开始调查总统
Jaye, start that database on our President.
我们得知道总司令到底怎么了
We'll find out what's going on with our Commander-in-Chief.
他的所作所为不像我们所认识的总统
He's not acting like the man we know.
找出这个原因  我们就能恢复身份了
We find out why, we can start being soldiers again.
杰伊女郎中尉  请求紧急救援
Lieutenant Lady Jaye, requesting immediate aid.
如果有任何幸存下来的特种兵
If any Joes have survived...
这个频道只有特种兵能收到对吧
This channel's restricted to Joes, isn't it?
波多马克河的西面
Magnetic west of the Potomac.
他们还活着
They're alive.
我是杰伊女郎中尉  请求紧急救援
This is Lieutenant Lady Jaye requesting immediate aid.
杰伊女郎中尉  我们是金克斯和蛇眼
Lieutenant Lady Jaye, this is Jinx and Snake Eyes.
我们正在追捕白幽灵
We are in pursuit of Storm Shadow.
即便蛇眼和金克斯抓到了白幽灵
Even if Snake Eyes and Jinx grab Storm,
他们也还在地球的另一边
they're still halfway around the world.
我们只能靠自己
We're on our own.
足够打一场战役了
Enough for a battle.
但不够打一场战争
Not a war.
我们要打的是场硬仗
We're fighting uphill here.
我14岁来到这里
I came here when I was 14
之前以为只能活到13岁
with a life expectancy of 13.
我从一个家迁到另一个家  直到这里
I was bounced around from home to home, until this
成为了我的家
became my home.
那些人在门口排着队找我打架
Guys were lined up outside that door to fight me.
皮包骨的我被揍得多了  就乐在其中了
They whooped my skinny ass so much I started to enjoy it.
直到有一年冬天
Till one winter,
我长高了20公分  重了27公斤
I grew 8 inches and gained 60 pounds.
我把一个人打得连胳膊都抬不起来
I punched a guy so hard he couldn't move his arm to tap out.
后来特种部队来这一带招人的时候
Then when the Joes came recruiting to the hood,
我已经将他们中的一半人都打倒了
I'd already beaten down half of it.
我成为了一名实地作战的特种兵
I became a Joe to serve. In the field.
所以如果我们打的是硬仗  那就硬打吧
So if we're fighting uphill, we take the hill.
我查到一些你们感兴趣的东西
Hey, I got something you'll want to see.
看看我调查总统的时候发现了什么
During my check of the President, look what I found.
这是8月9日的总统
This is the President on August 9th.
对海外能源的依赖
an addiction to offshore energy,
令我们某种程度上被迫卷入了
where we're forced to be kind of embroiled
外国的内政之中
in the affairs of foreign nations.
这是10天后
And this is 10 days later.
我是说  不然我们就有点
I mean, otherwise, we're sort of...
这是讲话中的补白
These are conversational fillers.
我们会蹦出一些无实意的词以使大脑
Little phrases we spit out to give our brain a chance
能赶上嘴巴  比如
to catch up with our mouth. Like...
- "比如"这个词  - 对
- Like. - Yes.
那总统怎么了
And our President?
8月9日到19日之间
Between August 9th and August 19th,
他不再使用"你知道""某种程度"
he stopped using "you know" and "kind of"
转而使用"我是说""有点"
and started using "I mean" and "sort of."
还不止这些  "晚饭"变成了"晚餐"
But that's not all. "Supper" became "dinner."
"苏打水"换成了"汽水"
"Soda" became "pop."
一个总统  行为却不同
One President, two fingerprints.
不过这也就几句话而已吧  这能...
But it's a few words, right? I mean, how much can...
看这个
Check this out.
两次新闻发布会  7月31日  9月1日
Two press conferences, July 31st, September 1st.
你看到他手指交叉的方式了吗
See his fingers clasped?
一张左手拇指在上  一张右手拇指在上
Left thumb on top versus right thumb on top.
同一个人绝不会有两种交叉方式
The same person never does this differently,
感觉会不对
it feels wrong.
有没有可能现在的总统
What if the President
不是总统本人
isn't the President?
如果我们的总司令是假的
Look, if the Commander-in-Chief is an imposter
下令袭击的人又是他
and he's the one that ordered the attack,
我们就必须假定任何人都不可信
we have to assume that there's no one we can trust.
有一个人可信
There is one man.
特种部队的名称就是由他而来
He's the reason we call ourselves Joes.
有人吗
Hello?
我要两盒薄荷巧克力  一盒查克拉
I'll take two cases of Thin Mints and a box of Chuckle Lucks.
放下武器
Lower your weapons.
科尔顿将军  请允许我
General Colton, if I may...
闭嘴  布伦达
Shut your mouth, Brenda.
我不叫布伦达
My name's not Brenda.
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in?
长官  对不起
Sir, apologies.
- 我是马文中士  - 我知道你是谁
- Sergeant Marvin... - I know who you are.
那您也一定知道我为什么会来这儿
Then you know why I'm here.
我不是没听见你们说什么
It's not like I don't hear what you're saying.
不过你说总统是假的吗
But an imposter President?
为什么将军说出来就听起来像疯话呢
How come when the General says it, it sounds crazy?
他们把真正的总统怎么了
What did they do with the real President?
我们担心他已经死了
We fear he's dead.
我不这么认为  没人会杀最有利的棋子
I don't think so. You're not going to kill your best asset.
康拉德·豪泽尔 公爵
"Conrad Hauser. Duke."
你们的队长
Your captain.
告诉我他是怎样一个人
Tell me one thing you know about him.
好战士
Great soldier.
挚友
Better friend.
而且他救了我的命  长官
And he saved my life, sir.
好的
Good.
你们说的是叛国之罪
What you're proposing is treason.
需要更多的证据才能开展行动
I'm gonna need something a little more to go on
光拇指交叉这点是不够的
than overlapping thumbs.
你在退休之前  曾经在一个安全委员会
Before you retired, you served on a security commission
与总统的参谋长共事
with the President's Chief of Staff.
科尔顿将军  你能让我们接近他吗
General Colton, can you get us close?
不行
Negative.
在这个城市里我不可能
I can't scratch my ass
有所行动还不被监视
in this town without getting on the watch list.
布伦达  把那支钢笔递给我
Brenda, hand me that pen.
刚才是女童子军  现在是秘书
Girl Scout to secretary.
真棒  我不叫布伦达
Amazing. Name's not Brenda.
递支笔而已
It's just a pen.
乔治敦  K大街  晚上9点
Avenue K, Georgetown. 9:00 p.m.
参谋长会去那里打牌
There's a poker game with the Chief of Staff there.
他牌打得很烂
He's not a good poker player.
破绽百出
He's got 1,000 tells.
我们只需要一个破绽
We only need one.
亲爱的
Hey, hon.
刚打完牌  算是花钱买教训了
Just got out of poker. Poorer but wiser.
实际上今天还不错
It was a good day, actually.
总统又开始吃他那些奇怪的药片了
The Prez was taking his crazy pills again.
宝贝  我回头打给你
Baby, I'm gonna have to call you back.
爱你
Love you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
需要帮你提袋子吗
You need a hand with your bags?
好啊
Sure.
没问题  好了
No problem. There you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
谁说好男人都死光了
Who said chivalry is dead, right?
好男人
Chivalry.
你要是那么说  我就有麻烦了
Talk like that, I'm gonna get myself in trouble.
我们去哪
Where we heading?
就到那边的街角
Just right around the corner.
那阵刺痛感是异戊巴比妥
That tingly feeling is amobarbital.
是能造成顺行性遗忘的镇静剂
It's a sedative that causes anterograde amnesia.
五分钟后你就会睡着
In five minutes, you're gonna be asleep.
再过五分钟
In another five,
你就会醒过来  根本不记得我这个人
you're gonna wake up with no idea I ever existed.
有没有发现你老大不对劲
Notice anything strange about your boss?
也许吧  怎么了
Maybe. Why?
因为你得帮我们打个电话
'Cause you're gonna make a phone call for us.
好让我们能接近他
Get us close to him.
不过别担心  你会忘了发生的这一切
But don't worry. You're gonna forget everything,
所以你的良心不会受谴责
so your conscience will be clear.
你为什么这么做
Why are you doing this?
我告诉你你也不会相信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
快打电话
Make the call.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
总统先生最近春风得意
El Presidente is on a roll.
他的数字上去了
His numbers are up.
我说的可不只是他的年龄
And I'm not just talking about his age.
我是不会说我们的总司令已经老了
Now, I'm not gonna call our Commander-in-Chief old.
实际上  他有一天打电话来问我的建议
Actually, he called me the other day for some advice.
- 晚上好  - 晚上好
- Good evening. - Good evening.
他想把国家的核武库
He wanted to hook up the nation's nuclear arsenal
装上声控开关
to the Clapper.
抱歉  女士  您
I'm sorry, ma'am, you're...
迟到了  我知道
Late, I know.
我耗费了一个军队的兵力才打扮好
Imagine the army it takes to make me look like this.
恕我无礼  我真想在那支军队的名单上
Forgive me. That's an army I'd like to enlist in.
说到名单
Speaking of lists,
您能否解释下为什么您不在我们的名单上
would you like to explain why you're not on ours?
在这儿呢  参谋长
Here she is. Chief of Staff.
玩得开心点  范德沃特小姐
Enjoy your evening, Miss Vandervoort.
我进来了
I'm in.
收到  待命
Roger that. Standing by.
杰伊
Jaye?
当心点  注意安全
You keep your head down. Be safe.
卡维尔先生友好地提到了
Mr Carville was nice enough to mention
我热衷的事项之一  核裁军
one of my passions. Nuclear disarmament.
几天之后
In just days,
世界八大核国家的领袖
the leaders of the world's eight nuclear nations
将齐聚历史悠久的萨姆特堡
will gather at historic Fort Sumter
召开核峰会
for a nuclear summit.
但是在原子八国共商大事前
But before the Atomic Eight break bread,
我们先来
it's our turn.
谢谢你  詹姆斯  非常感谢
Thank you, James. Thank you so much.
总统先生  我是福克斯新闻的艾米·范德沃特
Mr President. Amy Vandervoort, Fox News.
福克斯  当然了
Fox, of course.
所以你看起来才那么"公平公正"(福克斯新闻的口号)
That's why you look so "Fair and balanced."
很有趣  不过我希望能
Very cute. But I was actually hoping to have a...
跳支舞?
Dance?
我本来想说  引用您的一句话
I was going to say, quote.
好  听着
Okay, here's a quote.
在我的核峰会之后世界就会改变
The world will change after my nuclear summit.
我们跳支舞怎么样
How about we dance?
真的  我不会跳舞
I really, I don't dance.
抱歉
Sorry.
谢谢  总统先生  您给了我所需要的
Thank you, Mr President. You gave me what I need.
不过我得回去赶稿了
But I really have to make my deadline.
- 很高兴见到您  - 谢谢你
-It's been a pleasure. - Thank you.
你好吗
How are you?
很好  先生
Good, sir.
我从他的上衣取到一根头发  希望够了
I got a strand of hair from his jacket. I hope it's enough.
快点
Come on.
收到
Copy that.
等待身份验证
Standing by for I.D.
所有部门  进入橙色预警  待命
All units, setting condition orange. Stand by.
我不接受拒绝
I don't take no for an answer.
快好了
Almost there.
加油  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
扎坦
Zartan?
杰伊  赶快离开那里
Jaye, get out of there now.
我的老天
Oh, my God.
有不明身份者  她是特种兵
We have an unauthorised I.D. She's a Joe.
有特种兵出现
We have a Joe on the premises.
杰伊
Jaye.
杰伊  快走
Jaye, now.
我出来了
I'm out.
执行B计划  去B地点会合
Plan B, rendezvous Bravo.
不行  去C地点会合
Negative. Proceed to rendezvous Charlie.
C地点
Charlie.
这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
非常抱歉  杰伊
Sorry, Jaye.
接下来我全盘接手
I got it from here.
别
Don't.
我们有证据了  可以拿去给乔·科尔顿
We have proof. We're taking it to Joe Colton.
这事你自己早已计划好了吗
You planned this all along.
虎爷  退下
Block, stand down.
我们不是律师  我们是战士
We ain't lawyers. We're soldiers.
我说过要找出幕后主使
I told you I was gonna find the man who did this.
我打算杀了他
I was gonna kill him.
不  不  不行
No! That's... No. Negative!
虎爷  虎爷
Block. Block.
他奶奶的
Damn it!
一枪毙命
One in the chamber.
虎爷  虎爷  你在哪里
Block? Block, where are you?
我要看的就是那表情
I want to see that face.
知道自己死期将至的表情
The one where you realise today's the day.
可爱的小兵们在沙漠里被我点烟花一样
It's the face all those pretty little Joes had in the desert
点着时  脸上都有这个表情
when I lit them all up like fireworks!
我真想看到那表情
I really want to see that face.
就是这个
There it is.
如果眼镜蛇和扎坦都在白宫里
If Cobra and Zartan are in the White House,
那世界就危险了
then the world is at stake.
白幽灵
Storm Shadow
说出眼镜蛇的最终计划
You will tell us Cobra's endgame,
不然就用你杀害师傅的刀将你斩杀
or die by the same sword you once used to kill our master.
你的刀
Your sword,
我们敬爱的哈德大师赐予你的刀
given to you by our beloved Hard Master.
你是否承认  是嫉妒与憎恨让你
Do you deny that your envy and hatred drove you to shed
杀害了哈德大师
the Hard Master's blood?
当憎恨多到无以复加
It's possible to feel so much hate
便会对之麻木
you stop feeling it at all.
就像鱼在水中而不自知
Like a fish not knowing it's in water.
但我的宿命早已被他人注定
But my path was chosen for me
包括我的敌人
by my enemy
他们杀害哈德大师后嫁祸于我
who framed me for killing the Hard Master.
还有我的朋友
And my friends
相信这骗局的朋友
who believed it.
对双眼被蒙蔽之人  为何徒劳去辩解
Why defend yourself to men too blind to see?
血是哈德大师的没错
That is the Hard Master's blood.
但那把
But that is not...
等一下
Wait!
不是我的刀
my sword.
岚影一族之刃是不会断的
Arashikage steel does not break.
我一遍又一遍地自问
I have asked myself over and over
谁如此蔑视我  甚至要毁我一生
who despised me enough to destroy my life?
对不起  白幽灵
I am sorry, Storm Shadow.
但陷害你之后
But who would stand to gain the most
谁是最大的得利者呢
by framing you for this crime?
令你亡命天涯的年轻对手
Your young adversary who chased you away?
还是将落魄的你收留的那人
Or the man into whose arms you were chased.
那人接纳了你
Someone who welcomed you,
好心对你
showed you kindness.
他需要我
He needed me.
因为我将成为那种人
For who I would become.
成为身怀绝技的愤怒勇士
A warrior of great skill and anger.
陷害我的人诡计多端
The man who betrayed me was capable of great ingenuity,
崇尚暴力
violence,
更重要的是
but most of all,
善于伪装
disguise.
扎坦
Zartan.
没错
Yes.
告诉我们他和眼镜蛇的计划
Tell us what he and Cobra have planned.
好让我们齐心协力歼灭
So we can destroy our common enemy
共同的敌人
together.
别动
Try to hold still.
你要不要再说一遍指关节该怎么攻击
You want to remind me how knuckles are supposed to strike again?
要团结一致
Together.
这些都是你说的
Those were your words.
- 我只是见机行事  - 别掩饰
- I had a shot and I took it. - Now, don't give me that!
你已经胡来了
You went rogue.
我还会这样做的
And I'd do it again.
是吗  接下来你还有什么大计划
Yeah? And what was your big plan, then, huh?
去自杀吗
You get yourself killed?
我的老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.
我对你唯命是从
I listened to everything you said over and over again.
从来不过问
I never questioned...
我不想再牺牲战友
I wasn't going to bury any more Joes.
我要大开杀戒
I've got guns to clean.
帮我拉下拉链
Help me out here?
谢了
Thanks.
要是我爸能看到我现在的样子就好了
If my dad could see me now...
为什么这么说
What are you talking about?
他一定不相信
He wouldn't believe it.
为什么
Why?
我家三代从军
Third generation military.
他做梦都想第四代也从军  然后
Desperately wanted a fourth, and
我妈就生了我
my mom had me.
那他一定很为你感到骄傲
Well, he must be real proud of you, then.
他不信任女军人
He didn't believe in female soldiers.
我终于鼓起勇气问他原因时  他说
I finally asked him why. He said
他不想将自己的性命交到一个女人手上
he didn't want to put his life in the hands of a woman.
第二天我就入伍了
I enlisted the next day.
努力了七年
Spent the next seven years
只为了军衔超过他  好让他向我敬礼
trying to outrank him so he'd have to salute me.
成功了吗
Did it work?
在那之前他就去世了
He died before I got the chance.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我会怀念刚才穿红衣的你
I'm actually gonna miss the red.
你美极了
You look real nice.
我说了  要大开杀戒
Hey. I said we got guns to clean.
这世界自己救不了自己
The world ain't saving itself.
那一下是因为你的加税法案
That was for the tax hike.
说得好像你缴过税似的
Like you pay taxes.
我是替众人不平
Ain't always about me.
够了够了
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
留着他还有用
We still need the man.
况且  打在他身  痛在我心啊
Besides, we've grown close.
白幽灵能来吗
Is Storm Shadow in?
你不用担心他  他一定能来
Don't you worry about him. He'll be more than ready.
你的内阁班子看来不怎么样
I'm not too impressed with your Cabinet.
又没通过听证会  凑合着用吧
No confirmation hearings, that's what you get.
够了
Enough!
由我来接手
I'll take it from here.
控制这个手提箱的人
He who controls this briefcase,
就能控制美国核武库
controls the U.S. nuclear arsenal
以及全人类的命运
and the fate of humanity.
张开眼睛  前总统先生
Open your eyes, Mr Ex-President.
眼睛是心灵的窗户
The eyes are the windows to the soul.
张大点
Open up.
宙斯已经造好了
Zeus is ready.
万事俱备  只欠东风
We just need one final piece of the puzzle.
干得好
Well done.
历史自有公断
History will stand in judgment.
可惜断的不是我  是你
Not of me. Of you.
情况如何  杰伊
What do we got, Jaye?
扎坦全神贯注于这个核峰会
Zartan's entire focus has been this nuclear summit.
这一定是他计划的关键
It has to be the key to whatever he's planning.
好吧  那就是我们的目标了
All right. Well, then that's our target.
没错
Yeah.
伙计们  起来
Guys, move.
这次我比你快了  蛇眼
I think I'm faster than you, Snake Eyes.
该死的忍者
Damn Ninjas.
见到你太好了  兄弟
Good to see you, brother.
我是杰伊
Jaye.
我是金克斯
Jinx.
退后
Back up.
他是我们这边的
He's with us.
我可不是你们这边的
I am not with you.
只是这一次
But for this once,
我不是敌人而已
I am not against you.
他杀了我们多少人
How many of our men has he killed?
我们难道要和他并肩作战吗
We're supposed to fight with him?
世界各国的首脑明天将召集  那是陷阱
The leaders of the world will gather tomorrow. It's a trap.
只有白幽灵知道眼镜蛇的计划
Storm is the only one who knows Cobra's plan
他了如指掌  能帮我们设法阻止那计划
inside and out. He can help us find a way to stop it.
但我们必须合作
But we have to work together.
好吧
All right.
行动
Let's move.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
搞不好你的邻居也藏了不少货
Makes you wonder about your neighbours.
帅气
Nice.
翻开那个沙发
Open up that couch.
有需要吗
Anything?
我自有准备
I brought my own.
好刀
Nice.
就是它了
Yeah, that'll work.
那支是我的
That one's mine.
这真是巴顿将军的枪  没错吧
This really is Patton's gun, isn't it?
他家人送我的礼物
Gift from his family.
无上的荣耀
What an honour.
没错
You bet.
我在考虑给你弄个配得上你的大家伙
I was actually thinking about something a little more your size.
可别给我刮花了
Try not to scratch her up.
挂空档时候会有点问题
Idles a little rough in neutral.
我不挂空档
I ain't gonna be in neutral.
你也来吗
What about you?
国防部说我不可以复出
DOD says I can't come out of retirement.
他们可没说我不能重新入伍
They didn't say anything about reenlisting.
向你报到  军士长
Reporting for duty, Sergeant Major.
我想带上一群老伙计
I'd like to bring a couple friends of mine.
科尔顿的队伍  很荣幸见到你们
Colton's team, it's our honour.
你们负责守边界
You guys take the perimeter.
火石  杰伊  蛇眼  你们负责边翼
Flint, Jaye, Snake, you guys take the flank.
金克斯和白幽灵  你们做内应
Jinx and Storm, Trojan Horse.
扎坦会提着手提箱
Zartan will be holding the briefcase.
白幽灵会是最接近他的人
Storm will be the closest man to him.
但直到我们都就位  他才能行动
But he can't move until we're all in position.
每个人都给我盯着手提箱
Everyone keep your eye on the prize.
抢到它  世界就安全了
We secure the football, we secure the world.
蛇眼  觉得怎么样
Snake, how's all that sound?
我猜也是
That's what I thought.
稍微等一下
Okay, wait. Hold on a second.
这里  这里和这里仍然有敌人的装甲车
We still have enemy armour here, here, and here.
对吧
Right?
这些坦克不除  我们就完了
These tanks survive, we don't.
坦克我来解决
Leave the tanks to me.
将军
General?
叫我乔
Call me Joe.
- 我有遗漏吗  - 没有
- Anything I missed? - No.
滴水不漏  我的任务是什么
Rock solid. My orders?
解救总统
The President.
- 布伦达和我一组  - 收到
- Brenda's with my team. - Roger that.
布伦达有权选择吗
Does Brenda get a vote?
没有
Negative.
你又需要人递笔吗
You need a pen?
我需要你的一臂之力
I need your help.
好吧
All right.
让我们大干一场
Let's kick that ass! Hoo-ah!
在这历史性的一天
A historic day
美国总统将会见
for the President of the United States as he meets with...
今天下午  总统将会见
This afternoon, the President is meeting with
八大核国家的领袖
the leaders of the eight nuclear powers.
从未有哪位总统如此大胆地
Never before has a President been so bold
邀请所有领导人同聚一堂
to call the leaders of the world together...
这种史无前例的核会谈
These are unprecedented nuclear talks that
以往被认为永远不可能发生
most believed would never happen.
毫无疑问  会谈的警戒将是最高级别的
You can bet security is at its highest...
我们也许比任何时期更接近无核世界
We may be closer to a nuclear-free world than we have ever been.
各位领导人
My fellow world leaders,
欢迎来到萨姆特堡的神圣土地
welcome to the hallowed grounds of Fort Sumter,
我们国家万恶的内战
whose proud walls saw the first shots
就是在这里打响了第一枪
in our nation's grievous Civil War.
人们曾在这里疯狂地穿过工事上的缺口
Here, men rushed through the breach in a madness.
但如果我们退一步  摒弃自己的恶欲
What better place to step back from that same breach.
原谅我们的死敌
Renounce our darker natures.
这个世界将变得更美好
Forgive our staunchest foes.
这里是一个象征
This site is symbolic.
不仅仅象征着我们谋求的和平
Not only for the peace we seek to achieve,
也象征着我们要避免的灾难
but the conflagration we seek to avoid.
我们现今的卫士眼镜蛇部队坚信
The Cobras who protect us today are dedicated to the belief
心态的平和才是最高境界的和平
that there is no greater peace than peace of mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
我再说一次
I'll say it again.
核武器的存在能让世界更安全
The world is safer with a nuclear presence.
相信你的选民也会满意我们的最终提案
I'm sure your electorate will be happy by our final proposal.
2016年前裁减至一半
50% reduction by 2016.
在场有许多国家的领袖
There are a lot of leaders in this room.
但只有一位来自自由世界的领导人
But only one leader of the free world.
而他
And he,
也就是我本人  别走神
I, stay with me,
要求在座各位全面销毁核武器
asked you here with the goal of universal disarmament.
共创无核世界
Nuclear zero.
我本来打算来软的
Now, I was prepared to cajole to get what I want.
现在我要来硬的
I'm now at threaten.
所有人立即销毁所有库存核武器
Each of you will clear out his nuclear closet immediately.
不照做的将被视为宣战行为
Failure to participate will be considered an act of war.
开什么玩笑
You're joking, of course.
这次峰会结束了
This summit is over.
那就到此为止吧
Then this is it.
到此为止了  小子们
This is it, boys.
这个国家向你们宣战
This country is at war.
向你  你  你  你  还有你
With you and you and you and you and you and you.
D队就位  E队  开始行动
Delta team in position. Echo, you're a go.
这里是E队  准备进攻
This is Echo. Beginning assault.
美国核武库
The U.S. nuclear arsenal
足以把你们每个国家摧毁14次以上
is capable of destroying each of your countries 14 times over.
确切的说  能摧毁朝鲜15次
Fifteen, in the case of North Korea, just to be sure.
这一切
And all
只需按下
at the push
一个按钮
of a button.
这是真的
It's true.
没错  我按下去了
Yeah, I pressed it.
你疯了
You have lost your mind!
只是相对而言
It's all relative.
给你们3分钟时间考虑
You got three minutes to decide.
- 你轮下一班吗  - 无线电保持静音
- You got next watch? - Maintain radio silence.
我们不能再坐视不理
We cannot, we will not leave a legacy of acquiescence!
把手提箱拿来
Bring the briefcase.
别这样
Don't do this!
这对谁都没好处
There can be no winners!
最高分啊
High score.
历史会见证  谁该为这疯狂之举负责任
Let history record who was responsible for this madness.
发射
Launch.
已看到翡翠城
Eyes on the Emerald City.
杰伊和科尔顿  总统解救行动开始
Jaye and Colton, you're a go for POTUS.
(总统行宫)
你还好吧
You all right?
没事  你呢
Yeah. You all right?
胆固醇有点高
My cholesterol's a little high.
这里是杰伊和科尔顿将军  搞定岗哨
Jaye and General Colton. Checkpoint neutralised.
自已保重
You're on your own.
好消息是下个月不用开全球变暖峰会了
Well, the good news is, no global warming summit next month.
除非
Unless
我们其中有人在意他的历史地位
one of us cared enough about his place in history
愿意单方面摧毁自己的弹头
to unilaterally disable his warheads.
就当是为了子孙后代
You know, in the name of the children.
有人要自告奋勇吗
Any volunteers?
没有吗  好吧
No? Fine.
我来
Me.
打电话确认一下
Call your people to confirm.
你真是个疯子
You're a complete lunatic.
将要摧毁亚洲的可是你
Says the man about to destroy Asia.
有人跟风吗
Come on, who's going to follow suit, huh?
你们打算眼睁睁地看着地球毁灭吗
Are you really going to stand by and watch as Earth is destroyed?
我们终止
Abort!
(法国  洲际导弹已毁)
估计就剩朝鲜没按了
I figured North Korea for last.
小伙子真讨人喜欢
Got to love the little guy.
各位
Gentlemen.
欢迎来到无核世界
Welcome to a nuclear-free world.
留心看你们祖国的实况图像
I want to direct your attention to live images of your homelands.
现在大家看到的是一套先进的武器系统
Now, you're looking at an advanced weapons system
叫宙斯计划
we call Project Zeus.
一共有7颗宙斯卫星环绕地球飞行
There are seven Zeus satellites orbiting Earth.
每颗卫星都有10根中空的铂金管
Each satellite contains 10 hollow platinum tubes
每根管里填充着一根钨棒
filled with a tungsten rod.
宙斯卫星1A到达伦敦
Zeus satellite 1-A approaching London.
准备就绪  等待空投批准
Ordnance live and loaded. Awaiting drop authorisation.
为了让钨条击中目标
Now, to direct a rod to its target,
我们不需要发射
we don't launch it or fire it.
我们进行空投
We drop it!
只靠重力
Gravity does the rest.
看好了
Observe.
卫星1A  已获远程发射批准
Satellite 1-A. We have remote launch authorisation.
三  二  一
Three, two, one,
投放
drop.
钨棒到达地面的速度比子弹快8倍
A rod touches down eight times faster than a bullet.
杀伤力也远超于核弹头
And with a force significantly greater than a nuclear warhead.
不会产生放射性尘埃
None of the fallout.
只有无限的乐趣
All of the fun.
你必须对此负责
You will have to answer for this.
你的国会和法院会追究你的责任
To your Congress, your courts.
错了  是他们要听我的命令
Correction, they will have to answer to me.
你到底想要什么
What is it you want?
一切
I want it all.
眼镜蛇革命开始了
The Cobra revolution has begun.
扎坦按下按钮后已启动自动投放程序
By pressing that button, Zartan initiated an auto-drop sequence.
我的宙斯卫星正向着
My Zeus satellites are moving into position
其余6个国家飞去
over your six remaining countries.
卫星2A至7A正前往目标
Satellites 2-A through 7-A en route to targets.
按下同一个键  就能终止这一切
The same button that begins this can end it.
不过要付出代价
But I only press it for a price.
就是绝对的臣服
Total allegiance.
虎爷  搞定外围的敌人
Block, secure the perimeter!
从扎坦那儿把控制箱拿来
Get the control case from Zartan.
我要把他们全灭了
I'm going to drop them all.
往大门跑  快点
Head for the door, now! Go, go!
卫星正飞往目标
Satellites en route to targets.
开始执行指令程序
Beginning command protocols.
跟着地面部队  快
Follow that ground team! Go!
停
Stay.
在你的六点钟方向  眼镜蛇2号
On your six, Cobra two!
眼镜蛇1号  我无法锁定目标
Cobra one, Cobra one, I need eyes on! Eyes on!
惨了
Damn it.
我们把她逼到角落了
We've got her cornered.
她走投无路了
She ain't go anywhere.
走
Go!
白幽灵  没想到你加入了特种部队
Storm. I never figured you for a Joe.
我对你太失望了
I'm very disappointed in you.
你还真难打中
You're a bitch to hit.
叛徒
Traitor.
白幽灵
Storm.
这把刀从来不适合
You know, this sword was never intended
控制不了自己怒火的人使用
for anyone with anger management issues.
- 什么声音  - 别吵
- What was that? - Shut up.
- 雷  - 是的  长官
- Ray? - Yes, sir.
去门口看一下  回来汇报情况
Check the door. Give me a sit rep.
我这就去
I'm on it.
你们俩守住入口
You two secure the entrance.
- 你要干嘛  - 跟我走  离开这里
- What are you doing? - Let's go. We're out of here.
别过来  不然我就开枪
Stand down. I'm gonna shoot him!
我说了别过来
I said stand down!
乖乖放下武器  让我们离开
Be a good G.I. Joe and drop the gun. We're walking out of here.
不然我就朝他脑袋开枪  听见没
I will shoot him in the head. Do you understand me?
你们都聋了吗  把枪放下
You're not listening, are you? Put the gun down!
丢掉武器
Drop them.
没事了  放轻松
Easy, easy.
按住伤口
Put some pressure on it.
科尔顿将军
General Colton.
- 很高兴见到你  - 我也是
- It's good to see you. - Good to see you.
- 抱歉  总统先生  - 没事
- Sorry, Mr President. - No, it's fine.
我们走吧
Come on. Let's move.
走吧
Here we go.
拦路虎  总统获救  无人伤亡
Roadblock, POTUS secure. No casualties.
收到了  杰伊
Roger that, Jaye.
你背叛了哈德大师
You betrayed the Hard Master.
还把我变成了今天这个样子
And made me what I am.
是的
Yep.
我也知道那是错的
Yeah, I can see that was wrong.
我们要尽快找到萤火虫和眼镜蛇
We need eyes on Firefly and Cobra ASAP.
院子找遍了  没看见他
Courtyard clear. No sign of him.
指挥官  我拿到箱子了
Commander, I have the case.
可按原计划进行
We are still a go.
离空投还有多久
How long till drop?
与原计划相符  指挥官  还有五分钟
On schedule, Commander. Five minutes to live fire.
最终锁定即将开始
Final targeting to begin shortly.
宙斯卫星4号和7号已就位
Zeus satellites 4 and 7 in position.
卫星2  3  5  6号已锁定目标
Zeus satellites 2, 3, 5, and 6 are locked on target.
法国  俄罗斯  朝鲜
France, Russia, North Korea,
印度  以色列  中国
India, Israel, China.
虎爷
Block.
眼镜蛇指挥官逃了
Cobra Commander's bugging out.
没看见萤火虫
No sign of Firefly.
我看到他了
I've got him.
目标已锁定  武器装载中
Targets acquired. Ordnance live and loading.
宙斯4号已做好发射准备  舱口已打开
Zeus 4 is ready to fire. Hatch is open.
- 搞定他  - 干掉他
- Get him! - Take him out!
想要拿箱子
You want that case?
先得过我这一关
You're gonna have to come through me.
没错
That's right.
所有卫星开始装弹  准备倒计时
All satellites have begun load for final countdown.
发射密码确认
Launch codes confirmed.
倒数10秒发射
Ten seconds to live fire.
十
Ten.
九
Nine.
八
Eight.
七  六
Seven. Six.
五
Five.
四
Four.
三
Three.
二
Two.
(手控终止)
危机解除
Threat terminated.
B队  外围已安全
Team Bravo, perimeter has been cleared and secured.
这里是特种部队
Joe Command to covert operations.
我们已控制外围
We have control of the perimeter.
医护人员已到场
Medical personnel are on the scene.
所有特种兵已归队
All Joes are accounted for.
准备回家
We're going home.
总统今日已安全回到总统办公室
The President is back safe in the Oval Office today,
为特种部队主持表彰典礼
presiding over a ceremony honouring the G.I. Joes.
随着世界恢复秩序
With the world back in order,
各地重建工作也已经展开
rebuilding has begun around the world.
这些站在我们身边的人
Those who stand beside us,
世人只知他们是特种部队
the world knows them as Joes.
我们还知道  他们是英雄
We know them as heroes.
金克斯
Jinx.
欢迎加入特种部队
Welcome to the Joes.
火石
Flint.
干得漂亮
Great job.
杰伊·伯内特上尉
Captain Jaye Burnett.
我和你父亲是战友
I served with your father.
他会为你感到骄傲
He'd be very proud of you.
女士们  先生们  向特种部队致敬
Ladies and gentlemen, the G.I. Joes.
留给你找到眼镜蛇指挥官的时候用
For when you find Cobra Commander.
去哪里能找到你  将军
Where can we find you, General?
给我下命令就行
Just need my orders.
我们的组合可是所向无敌
You know, we'd make a hell of a team.